Vlatko Spirovski

North Macedonia, Gostivar



spirovski.14@gmail.com



+389 78 459 001



linkedin.com/in/vlatko-spirovski-637198196



18 October, 1999

Summary

Last year of studies - Engineering on Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering - UKIM. Someone who wants to upgrade and develop in Computer Science and programming languages (.NET) and Microsoft Dynamics. Experience for 3 months on project on Microsoft Dynamics CRM. Two times involved in Erasmus program in Bulgaria and Turkey. Rewards in math in High School.

Experience



Renting villa

Villa Beti - Mavrovo Aug 2018 - Present (4 years 5 months +)



✗ Software Developer Internship

Axapta Masters Oct 2022 - Dec 2022 (3 months)

Education



Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering - Skopje

Last year of studies, Computer Engineering Sep 2018 - Sep 2023

Skills

Working effectively within a team to accomplish key objectives.

Strong personal communication skills.

Ability to prioritise and work under pressure.

Microsoft Dynamics CRM • Microsoft Power Apps • .NET Framework • Databases • Object-Oriented • Programming (OOP) • MySQL • ASP.NET • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML5 JAVAScript

Vlatko Spirovski - page 1